## August Yadon

Cleveland, OH • (408) 609 0996 • AugustYadon@gmail.com

## Gameplay Programmer

C# Game developer, with an arsenal of tech experience and a thirst for learning.

As a critical thinker, I'll usually step back and think, what is our actual goal here, and is this the most practical way to accomplish this goal, or is this just our first idea? Are we choosing the technology for the solution we need, or are we bending our solution unnecessarily to fit our technology stack?

Technology tools include:

- C#
- Unity 3D
- SQL / Mongo DB
- VR (Virtual Reality)
- SteamVR Plugin
- Git etc.
- AR (Augmented Reality)
- AR Kit / AR Core / AR Foundations
- JavaScript / Node.js Steamworks libraries iOS and Android Development
  - Face Detection with Dlib

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

AIR EVERYWHERE, Kent, OH

Lead AR Developer III (October 2018 – July 2019) [C# - Unity - AR Kit]

Took conceptual ideas from the business side, and architected and built them into a reality.

Notable accomplishments:

- Led a dev team and challenged initial ideas to move them into an AR state of mind.
- Handled most of the physics based pieces, and 3D vector based problems.
- Improved the user experience with sounds/haptics/responsive interactions.

REWIND.SITE, NYC, NY

Backend Developer - Contract (June 2018 - October 2018) [C++ - Source Engine]

Completed tasks to bring new features to a CS:GO Demo Viewer platform

AUGGO DOGGO GAMES, Cleveland, OH

**Gameplay Programmer** (January 2017 – Present) [C# - Unity - SteamVR]

Created VR game - Plunker - Indie game development was performed entirely on Twitch.TV live. Notable Accomplishments:

- Created development tools, and powerful algorithms necessary for certain game mechanics.
- Created, textured, rigged, animated, voiced/audio engineered, and programmed all 3D assets.

NIMBLEFISH TECHNOLOGIES, San Francisco, CA

Software Engineer II (December 2014 – January 2017) [Node.js - Java - Bash]

Backend Plugin/Server Development, Data Processing Scripts, Test Driven Development

## **EDUCATION & CREDENTIALS**

CASE WESTERN RESERVE UNIVERSITY, Cleveland, OH

Bachelor of Science in Electrical Engineering, 2012